{
    "round0[hint]": {
        "says": [
            "Could you take a look at the difference of two consecutive numbers?",
            "What would be the next number of 2, 4, 6, 8, ..."
        ],
        "reply": [
            {
                "question": "10",
                "answer": "round1"
            }
        ]
    },
    "round0": {
        "says": [
            "Hi, this is Ada, I'm a chatbot.",
            "I\"m going to help you understand mathematical concept called \"sequences\".",
            "Why don't we start from an example?",
            "By the way, feel free to ask for a hint if you need some help!",
            "What would be the next number of 2, 4, 6, 8, ..."
        ],
        "reply": [
            {
                "question": "10",
                "answer": "round1"
            },
            {
                "question": "hint",
                "answer": "round0[hint]"
            }
        ]
    },
    "round1": {
        "says": [
            "\ud83d\udcaa We might need some terminologies before heading into more sequences:",
            "Ordered lists of numbers like these are called <span class=\"def\">sequences</span>. Each number in a sequence is called a <span class=\"def\">term</span>.",
            "<img src=\"resources/image/1-1.pn\" alt=\"sequence1-1\">",
            "Sequences usually have  <span class=\"def\">patterns</span> that allow us to predict what the next term might be.",
            "With these concept in mind, we can revisit our previous example.",
            "What is the 4th term of 2, 4, 6, 8, 10, 12, ..."
        ],
        "reply": [
            {
                "question": "8",
                "answer": "round2"
            },
            {
                "question": "hint",
                "answer": "round0[hint]"
            }
        ]
    },
    "round2": {
        "says": [
            "What is the 5th term of 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, ..."
        ],
        "reply": [
            {
                "question": "15",
                "answer": "round3"
            },
            {
                "question": "hint",
                "answer": "round0[hint]"
            }
        ]
    },
    "round3": {
        "says": [
            "It seems you have understand the concept of <span class=\"def\">term</span> pretty well!",
            "Did you notice there are three dots at the end of those sequence?",
            "Actually, it indicate that the sequence can be extended, even though we only see a few terms.",
            "What is the next term of 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, ..."
        ],
        "reply": [
            {
                "question": "18",
                "answer": "round4"
            },
            {
                "question": "hint",
                "answer": "round0[hint]"
            }
        ]
    },
    "round4[hint]": {
        "says": [
            "Well, I look into the first 3 terms and I think the pattern to generate next term is:",
            "Add five to the previous term.",
            "What would be the next term of 3, 8, 13, ?, ..."
        ],
        "reply": [
            {
                "question": "18",
                "answer": "round5"
            }
        ]
    },
    "round4": {
        "says": [
            "What would be the next term of 3, 8, 13, ?, ..."
        ],
        "reply": [
            {
                "question": "18",
                "answer": "round5"
            },
            {
                "question": "hint",
                "answer": "round4[hint]"
            }
        ]
    },
    "round5[hint]": {
        "says": [
            "This time the numbers become smaller and smaller!",
            "20 - 3 = 17, and 17 - 3 = 14. What would be the next?",
            "What would be the next term of 20, 17, 14, ?, ..."
        ],
        "reply": [
            {
                "question": "11",
                "answer": "round6"
            }
        ]
    },
    "round5": {
        "says": [
            "What would be the next term of 20, 17, 14, ?, ..."
        ],
        "reply": [
            {
                "question": "11",
                "answer": "round6"
            },
            {
                "question": "hint",
                "answer": "round5[hint]"
            }
        ]
    },
    "round6[hint]": {
        "says": [
            "On no, the difference between two consecutive terms change.",
            "But wait.. maybe we can get the next term by multiplying something?",
            "What would be the next term of 3, 6, 12, ?, ..."
        ],
        "reply": [
            {
                "question": "24",
                "answer": "round7"
            }
        ]
    },
    "round6": {
        "says": [
            "What would be the next term of 3, 6, 12, ?, ..."
        ],
        "reply": [
            {
                "question": "24",
                "answer": "round7"
            },
            {
                "question": "hint",
                "answer": "round6[hint]"
            }
        ]
    },
    "round7": {
        "says": [
            "I am convinced you are a prophet now!",
            "--- in terms of predicting next term.",
            "Great to talk to you today!",
            "See you later and let's explore more math!\ud83d\udc4b"
        ]
    }
}